{
  "author": "royal_flush",
  "rounds": [
    {
      "roundTitle": "Well, That Happened...",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Rishi Sunak is fined for failing to wear a seatbelt",
          "correctAnswer": "January"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Ncuti Gatwa stars as the Fifteenth Doctor in his first full series of 'Doctor Who'",
          "correctAnswer": "Trick question; that'll be 2024"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Humza Yousaf is appointed First Minister of Scotland",
          "correctAnswer": "March"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Pope Emeritus Benedict XVI dies aged 95",
          "correctAnswer": "Trick question; that was 2022"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The coronation of Charles III and Camilla takes place at Westminster Abbey",
          "correctAnswer": "May"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Roger Federer wins the Gentlemen's Singles final at Wimbledon",
          "correctAnswer": "Trick question; that was 2017"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "'Barbie' and 'Oppenheimer' are released worldwide",
          "correctAnswer": "July"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "England's Lionesses lose 1-0 to Spain in the final of the FIFA Women's World Cup",
          "correctAnswer": "August"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Elton John headlines Glastonbury Festival",
          "correctAnswer": "June"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The Rugby World Cup is won by South Africa in France",
          "correctAnswer": "October"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "'Now and Then', the so-called 'last Beatles song' is released and reaches #1 in the UK and USA",
          "correctAnswer": "November"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Following a ten-month tease, Linda is revealed as Keanu's murderer in 'EastEnders'",
          "correctAnswer": "December"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "April",
        "September",
        "February",
        "Trick question; that was 2021"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "Nested Media",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "A film within a 00s film",
          "correctAnswer": "Nation's Pride"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A play within a play",
          "correctAnswer": "The Murder of Gonzago"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A film within a 90s film",
          "correctAnswer": "Angels With Filthy Souls"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A book within a book",
          "correctAnswer": "The Theory and Practice of Oligarchical Collectivism"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A cartoon within a cartoon",
          "correctAnswer": "The Itchy & Scratchy Show"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A video game within a video game",
          "correctAnswer": "Crash Bandicoot"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A painting within a story within a book within a film",
          "correctAnswer": "Boy with Apple"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A newspaper within a comic",
          "correctAnswer": "The Daily Bugle"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A book within a video game",
          "correctAnswer": "Ruminations on the Elder Scrolls"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A TV show within a video game",
          "correctAnswer": "Address Unknown"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A musical within a musical",
          "correctAnswer": "Springtime for Hitler: A Gay Romp with Adolf and Eva at Berchtesgaden"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A TV show within a film",
          "correctAnswer": "The Truman Show"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Private Eye",
        "The Last of Us",
        "The Emancipation of Thought",
        "Knowing Me, Knowing You"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "That's A Typo...",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "The second of the 'five D's of dodgeball'",
          "correctAnswer": "Suck"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The capital city of Italy",
          "correctAnswer": "Rope"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Half of Laurel and Hardy",
          "correctAnswer": "Stay"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Band who performed the song 'Hold the Line'",
          "correctAnswer": "Togo"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "'Riotous' Stravinsky ballet: The ___ of Spring",
          "correctAnswer": "Rise"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Shakespearean stock character",
          "correctAnswer": "Tool"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Gradually takes away strength",
          "correctAnswer": "Sags"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Precipitation",
          "correctAnswer": "Rail"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Place of burial",
          "correctAnswer": "Tome"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "Shin",
        "Rest",
        "Trip"
      ]
    },
    {
      "roundTitle": "Here We Go Again...",
      "questions": [
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the things that will happen, or are expected to happen, in 2024",
          "correctAnswer": "UK general election"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the things that will happen, or are expected to happen, in 2024",
          "correctAnswer": "US presidential election"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the things that will happen, or are expected to happen, in 2024",
          "correctAnswer": "February 29th"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the things that will happen, or are expected to happen, in 2024",
          "correctAnswer": "The film 'Inside Out 2' is released"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the things that will happen, or are expected to happen, in 2024",
          "correctAnswer": "Trevor Noah hosts the Grammy Awards"
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Identify the things that will happen, or are expected to happen, in 2024",
          "correctAnswer": "The Games of the XXXIII Olympiad"
        }
      ],
      "redHerrings": [
        "French legislative election",
        "The film codenamed 'Avengers 5' is released",
        "Spain hosts the UEFA European Football Championship",
        "'Only Connect' begins its 17th series",
        "Sweden hosts the 69th Eurovision Song Contest",
        "500th episode of Royal_Flu$h's 'Game Night'",
        "Arctic Monkeys release the album 'The Car'",
        "Chris Rock hosts the Academy Awards",
        "The events of the film 'Blade Runner'",
        "Princess Eugenie gives birth to her second child with Jack Brooksbank"
      ]
    }
  ]
}